wareseeker.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy - WareSeeker

The the trust of our users is crucial to our business and WareSeeker is serious to regard the privacy of Internet users. 

If you have any concern about our products or website's privacy policies, please click here to contact us. We read every message submitted and try to reply to every one promptly. We may also file your comments to improve the program and site, or review and discard the information.

When a visitor requests pages from WareSeeker site, our Web servers automatically recognize the browser's domain name, and IP address. We collect the domain names and IP addresses in order to aggregate information on the pages users access or visit. This information is collected solely for statistical purposes and is not used to identify individuals.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. 

**When does WareSeeker collect personally- identifiable information?**  
WareSeeker will collect your information if the information is licensed to us, for example new released software subscription comes for users, software submission come from authors or order come from customers. We won't collect any personally- identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, phone number or email address from this web site without your knowledge, and will take measures to protect your privacy. 

In addition, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx). 

**How does WareSeeker use the information?**  
Once you licensed us provide a new released software list to you, we could send information to you via email daily, weekly or other post time. And you could easily remove your email address from our mail list. Once you submit some software to our download library, we could offer the products information and other available information to the users. Because of complaints about spamming, that email address is no longer included on our web pages and does not go out in New Upload Digests, etc. However we simply MUST have that email address anyway. It is because we will be forwarding messages, complaints, etc. from users and audience to that address and we may need to contact you about upload problems. Once you purchase products from us, additional information will be needed to fill your order. Any information provided will NOT be sold or given to any third party(ies) by any means, and will only be used for sending the Registration Information and the Free upgrade to you via email. Besides, if you send email to us for requesting help, your email address will only be used to send replies to you. 

**Links**  
WareSeeker contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we WareSeeker, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by WareSeeker.
